# Julian Martinez Gomez

## React Developer

Buenos Aires, ARG / +5491131291059 · julianmzg@gmail.com · https://julianmzg.com.ar · Linkedin

Fullstack Developer with over 4 years of experience in developing digital solutions using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Expert in leading teams and coordinating large-scale cultural events, managing projects from conception to execution. Proven ability to enhance product efficiency and functionality.

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

·Fullstack Development	Project Management and Technical Coord.	·Training in Algorithms and Logic
·Frontend Development	·Working in Multidisciplinary Teams	·Sound Design and Production
·Back-end Development	·User Experience Optimization	·Event Management &Production

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Fullstack Developer - Freelance**

Buenos Aires, ARG / 2020 - present

- · Developed over 15 complete websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, TypeScript, Node.js, and Next.js.
- · Collaborated directly with over 20 clients to turn their ideas into functional and attractive web applications.
- · Improved customer conversion rates by an average of 20% through the design and implementation of optimized user interfaces.

## Coordinator of Technical Production Area - Ministry of Culture, Argentina

Buenos Aires, ARG / 2020 - present

- · Coordinated the technical production of festivals and large-scale events across Argentina.
- · Managed events from planning to technical execution, ensuring impeccable results.
- · Implemented strategies to optimize production and reduce costs while maintaining high standards of quality and efficiency.

#### Music Producer / Sound Designer - Hybrid

ESP, URU, ARG / 2007 - present

- · Led artists and multidisciplinary teams to achieve results that emotionally resonate with each client.
- · Used advanced mixing techniques and specialized software to ensure professional quality in each production.
- · Contributed to over a dozen national and international projects, building client connections through music and production.

#### **Public Attention Manager - CCK**

**Buenos Aires, ARG** / 2016- 2019

- · Led public attention teams, managing visitor flows in spaces, concert halls, and auditoriums.
- · Coordinated and planned the attention for more than 3,000 daily visitors in the third-largest cultural center in the world.
- · Built relationships with top artists, officials, and public figures, ensuring a collaborative environment.

## **KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**

**Development of Complex Digital Solutions:** developed and deployed complex and highly functional websites using a wide variety of programming languages, frameworks, and advanced tools. Implemented optimized algorithms and efficient backend solutions, personally covering tasks and roles that typically require a full team.

**Coordination of Large-Scale Events:** successfully managed the technical production of public events for up to 100,000 people for over 4 consecutive years, leading numerous and diverse teams, achieving optimal results.

#### **EDUCATION**

- · Scientific Baccalaureate, Montevideo , Uruguay
- · Tertiary Education in Architecture, Universidad de la República, Montevideo, Uruguay

### **SKILLS**

Front-end: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | TypeScript | Next.js | TailwindCSS | Bootstrap |

**Back-end:** Node.js | Express | MongoDB | PostgreSQL | REST APIs

Others: Git | Github | AWS | Redux Toolkit | React-R-DOM | Zustand | Zod | Prisma | Docker

#### LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native | English: Fluent | Italian: Intermediate | Portuguese: Basic